

Candidate Web Developer

erkut.kaya@outlook.com

linkedin.com/erkut-kaya

Creative Skills

Teamwork

Googling

Problem Solving

erkut-kaya.github.io/Portfolio

Software Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

MS Office

SQL

Adobe Photoshop

Profile

I am a 4th year student of Computer Engineering department at Eskisehir Osmangazi University. I want to follow the technological developments in the field of technology and digitalization, make improvements in the system, improve customer satisfaction and loyalty, and improve the user experience.

Education

2021 - Present

Anadolu University (Eskisehir)

Business

Eskisehir Osmangazi University (Eskisehir)

Computer Engineering

2012-2016

Ertugrul Kurdoglu High School (Kocaeli)

Ibni Sina Primary School (İstanbul)

Experience

09/2021 - 10/2021

Intern / Anadolu University, Eskisehir

Focused on website design and software development using Html, Css, JavaScript, Excel and Adobe Photoshop.

07/2021 - 08/2021

Intern / Anadolubank, Istanbul

Built a representative web application of banking using Html, Css, JavaScript, Bootstrap.

Certificates

Front End Web Development Bootcamp

BTK Akademi

Project Management

BTK Akademi

Introduction to Social Media Specialist

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

BTK Akademi

Availability of Websites

Cisco

Networking Essentials

Hobbies

- Chess Walking
- Music
- Video Games
- Cycling Drawing

Preferences

Dr. Şahin IŞIK

Assistant Proffessor, Eskisehir Osmangazi University Email: sahini@ogu.edu.tr